Virginia Canals and Navigations Society Collection WLU.Coll.0172
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
Virginia Canals and Navigations Society Collection
1978-1983
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
Virginia Canals & Navigations Society, Inc.
Fletcher, Richard R.
WLU.Coll.0172
.8 Linear Feet
Scope and Contents
Records of the Society's research and meetings on river canals and boat traffic of nineteenth century Virginia from the collection of Richard R. Fletcher, Society Trustee. The collection includes the Society's publication The Tiller, >The Sweep
, research material, and correspondence.
Arrangement
Files in Box 1 arranged alphabetically by subject.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials in this collection are available for research use.
Canals; Virginia; Transportation; Correspondence; Research
- Miscellaneous
  - Control (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constitution and By-Laws (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from Richard Fletcher, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from Richard Fletcher, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence from Richard Fletcher, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence to Richard Fletcher, 1973-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence to Richard Fletcher, 1983-1987, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Financial records (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Meetings and projects (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Membership applications (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Membership lists (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Photographs (Box 1, Folder 13)
- The Sweep, 1995- (Box 2)
  - Poster and facsimile debt notes (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Publications of related (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Research materials (Box 2, Folder 16)
- The Tiller, 1980-2007 (Box 3)
- The Tiller, 2008 (Box 4)